♪ Men. ♪
Hey!
Oh, hey, morning, Berta.
Little warning, man at work.
Doing a little banging
and screwing.
Little warning for you.
Woman at bar until 2:00 a.m.
doing the same thing.
What are you doing?
I am baby-proofing
the house.
It's a requirement
of the adoption agency,
and it's a good thing, too.
This here kitchen
is a death trap.
Whole mess of things up in here
that can kill someone.
We got knives, we got fire,
poison, scalding hot water,
Alan's leftover fish tacos.
You worry too much.
Jake ate a steady diet
of floor wax and detergent,
and he turned out...
Yeah, maybe it's not a bad idea.
I locked all the cabinets
and the drawers,
put these safety knobs
on the stove,
and if you want to access
any chemicals,
you will need
a special magnetic key.
Oh, by the way,
when you're doing the laundry,
keep your eye out
for a special magnetic key.
Why would you need
to lock the towel drawer?
You hide your pot
in the medicine cabinet.
I'm guessing.
That is no ordinary
towel drawer.
That's the first step
on the stairway to disaster.
Oh, I'm too hungover
for this crap.
Okay, okay.
All right, imagine, if you will,
child pulls out the drawer,
climbs up onto the counter
and toddles over to the window
that has been left open
because Alan finds the smell
of steaming broccoli
to be "gaggy."
Whereupon, the child
spots a beautiful kite,
most likely in the shape
of a butterfly or a Pikachu.
The child reaches
for the kite,
tumbles out the window,
bounces off the awning,
flying through the air,
heading toward certain death,
when, miraculously, it is caught
by a shirtless
Matthew McConaughey.
"Don't worry,
your baby's gonna be all right,
all right, all right."
Yeah, sure.
You know what,
we got lucky this time,
but we can't depend
on McConaughey every time.
Okay, I'm gonna have to start
hiding the pot from you.
Better safe than sorry.
Every stairway, every toilet,
every sharp corner
has been locked,
latched or padded.
No one is getting hurt
in this house.
Hot!
Hot! Hot!
All right, all right,
all right.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 12x04 ♪
Thirty-Eight, Sixty-Two, Thirty-Eight
Original Air Date on November 20, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
So, as you can see,
I installed a gate
at the top of the stairs,
at the bottom of the stairs,
and as an extra precaution,
I put one in the middle
of the stairs.
Overachiever.
I think he's just trying
to keep me from getting away.
Well, you did a great job
baby-proofing.
I can't imagine anyone
getting hurt in this house.
Really? Try telling me
I look fat in these jeans.
Okay, flame off,
Human Torch.
So, uh, so, what do we do next?
Oh, well, it's pretty simple.
I walk out onto the deck,
you put a pile of hundreds
on the table,
I come back,
slip them into my purse,
and you get a kid.
I have $5,000 in the bottom
of a toolbox in the garage.
I was joking.
As was I.
Anyway, uh,
I wasn't gonna say anything
until you guys passed
the inspection,
but it looks like
we may have found
a potential match
for the two of you.
We're...
We're getting a baby.
Are you serious?
This is unbelievable.
Well, slow down;
all that's happened so far
is a pregnant mother has seen
your profile
and wants to meet you.
Somebody saw my profile
and wants to meet me?
That's so different
than the dating sites.
I can't believe this.
Who is she?
Where is she from?
How old is she? Is she
having a boy or a girl?
Wait, no, la-la-la-la-la!
I don't want to know.
I want to be surprised.
Walden, you're getting ahead
of yourself.
Did you say girl?
I thought I heard
you say girl.
Wait, no, you know what?
Doesn't matter.
Ten fingers and ten toes--
that's all that matters.
Are you not saying anything
'cause it's a boy?
Oh, my God,
we're having a boy!
Okay, Walden,
when you meet the mother,
you want to come off as a calm,
stable father.
Not like a 14-year-old girl
at a Justin Bieber concert.
Sorry,
we're just really excited.
No, I get it.
I'm excited for you.
I'll call you
when the meeting is set up.
Oh, and by the way,
I think you look fantastic
in those jeans.
Girl, we are gonna be BFFs.
We're gonna have a baby.
We're gonna have a baby!
Oh, we have to celebrate.
Uh, I'll go to the garage
and get some champagne.
Great! We're gonna have a baby!
We're gonna have a...
Wait, we don't have champagne
in the garage.
My toolbox!
Alan!
♪ Men. ♪
Here.
I got this for you.
Why?
I think it would be nice
if we wore matching sweaters
to meet the birth mom.
Twinsies.
We're supposed to be
a married couple,
not half of
a barbershop quartet.
Can't we be both?
♪ Miss McMartin,
bring me a kid ♪
♪ Bom-bom-bom-bom ♪
♪ Marrying you
was a dumb thing I did ♪
♪ Bom-bom-bom-bom. ♪
You were flat.
So, the mom--
you think she's hot?
She's nine months pregnant!
I know.
Love me some preggos.
38-62-38.
Baby got back and front.
Okay, listen.
If we want this girl
to give us her baby,
she has to think that
we're a well-adjusted couple.
If she gets a creepy vibe
off of you,
she's gonna turn and run
the other way.
And I'm only saying this
'cause I'm getting a creepy vibe
off of you.
Says the guy who Googled
"Helen Mirren nip slip."
Helen is timeless.
Now, listen.
If you mess this up for me,
I will make your life
a living hell.
Now, remember,
we love each other.
Hello, Mama.
Hi.
Hi, you must be Kathy.
Yes, uh, welcome to
our Malibu dream house.
He's Ken.
Oh, I guess that
makes me Barbie.
I'm Walden.
This is Alan.
Come in.
Here, c-can I take your coat?
Oh, thank you.
Wow!
Look at you!
So very pregnant.
Coat.
I know.
I haven't seen
my feet since July.
Am I wearing matching shoes?
Um...
actually, no.
Uh, but you know what, it works.
It's cute.
Um, please sit.
Yeah, please.
How you feeling?
My ankles are swollen,
my back hurts,
and forget about my breasts.
I haven't even noticed,
you know, 'cause I'm gay.
That's...
That's my rainbow warrior.
Always waving his flag.
Even when it relates
to nothing.
Um, so, uh,
tell us about Kathy.
I think the first thing
you should know about me
is this is not representative
of who I am.
See, I just graduated
from UCLA.
The baby is a result
of a spring break trip to Vegas.
Ah. I guess what happens
in Vegas
stays in Kathy.
Yep, took me about six weeks
to figure out
that my morning sickness
wasn't just
a really bad hangover.
Well, we all make mistakes.
One morning,
I woke up married to this one.
See, bottom line, this wasn't
part of my five-year plan.
You know, law school,
clerk for a judge,
start my own practice.
Wow, that's-that's impressive.
Uh, Alan's son, Jake,
had a five-year plan
for the tenth grade.
See, that's why I liked
your profile.
You have parenting experience.
Your sense of humor
came through.
And I kind of love
that you're gay.
Not as much as we do.
Right, Wally Bear?
That's right, Alley Cat.
Even though I'm not gonna
be part of the baby's life,
I like the idea of being
the only mom.
I can totally understand that.
Probably because my mom was an
ice-cold, sharp-tongue alcoholic
who preferred shopping and spas
over spending time with me.
And I can
totally understand that.
So, tell me about you.
What made you guys decide
to start a family?
Uh, well, raising my son
was one of the greatest
experiences of my life,
and I just wanted Walden
to feel that same joy.
Yeah, I mean, for me
it's a couple reasons.
I-I felt like something
was missing in my life,
and I wanted to give back,
and having a kid will allow me
to drive in the carpool lane.
It's nice to laugh again.
Except I just peed a little
on your sofa.
I'll get you something.
Oh, uh, actually,
I got something right here.
♪ Men. ♪
The baby just kicked.
I felt it.
Oh, looks like someone's got
a little soccer star in there.
God, you smell good.
Alan, you want to come up
for some air?
Oh, sorry.
Just got excited.
About the baby.
Sure.
So, uh, Kathy,
uh, do you know
if it's a boy or a girl?
I don't, but your profile said
you didn't have
a gender preference, right?
Oh, that's right.
Just like me in my 20s.
You guys crack me up.
You're gonna make great dads.
Oh, world's greatest, according
the coffee mugs I bought.
Well, that's good,
because I made up my mind.
I want you to have my baby.
No!
Yes.
Oh, my God!
You did not just say that!
You bitch!
Thank you, Kathy.
Thank you, Vegas.
Thank you, broken condom.
Well, you can thank
two-for-one tequila shots
at the Tropicana.
Let's not forget
this little guy.
Do you feel it moving?
I can feel it growing.
♪ Men. ♪
Okay, best shower gift:
Barry. Baby's first bong.
Yep.
And just like the kid's diaper,
it's full of
stinky green stuff.
The pizza's on its way.
In the meantime, uh,
who wants a beer?
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
There we go.
Walden, you are gonna
make a great dad.
Hey.
And, Alan,
you've already raised Jake,
so I guess just...
do the opposite.
I still can't believe
it's even possible
for two men to have a baby.
What an age we live in.
Science, right?
Larry, we're-we're not
actually having a baby.
We're adopting.
Ah, shooting blanks, huh?
Well, I guess
if Alan gets pregnant,
you'll know he's been
cheating on you.
So you two are
really married, huh?
Yep.
Yeah, crazy, isn't it?
No, I'll tell you what's crazy.
You have never
hit on me once, Walden.
I mean, we worked together
every day, side by side,
and not so much as
a lingering glance
or a "Gee, you look
nice today, Barry.
"You lost a little weight,
Barry?
Those cargo shorts really
flatter your calves, Barry."
No, man.
We got married
so I could adopt a baby.
That... we're a pretend couple.
It's kind of like your
"girlfriend in Canada."
Okay, Olivia is real.
I mean, just... Okay, look at
these nude photos she sent me.
That's Jennifer Lawrence.
She gets that all the time.
In a couple days,
I'm gonna be a dad.
I'm gonna be
completely responsible
for the emotional
and financial well-being
of someone who is
completely incapable
of taking care of themselves.
Thank you for being
my test baby.
I'd keep my fingers
crossed for a boy.
Why?
Well, basic math.
If you have a boy, you only
have to worry about one penis.
You have a girl, you have
to worry about them all.
Either way,
you're gonna love it.
Being a father is
the best thing in the world.
How old are your kids?
Well, my son is 15
and my secret daughter
is going to be 11 this year.
Your... your
secret daughter?
Yeah, she looks a lot
like my secret wife.
You know, kids are amazing.
You know? You get to pass
all this knowledge down
to this little person
and-and shape their mind.
Like, you know,
how to talk to girls
and how to be there for
your friends when they need you.
Oh, you can teach them
your ability
to always be in the bathroom
whenever the dinner check comes.
That's pure instinct.
Can't be taught.
You know, all my memories
revolve around my dad.
The time he threw my Tamagotchi
down the garbage disposal.
Time he made a pass
at my prom date.
Time he divorced my mom
and married my prom date.
Guys.
Guys, it's
the hospital.
Oh, if it's one of
my patients, I'm not here.
Oh, don't worry.
If I'm your
kid's doctor,
I won't do that.
It's what you say.
Kathy's in labor!
We got to go!
I'll get an Uber.
I'll go grab the car seat.
I'll get the
diaper bag.
Oh, God, that's the pizza guy.
Um... hey, Alan,
could you pay
the pizza guy?
I'm in the bathroom!
How does he do it?
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, you know,
I-I appreciate you guys coming,
but you really
don't have to stay.
Are you kidding?
We want to be here.
You know what
they say.
"To raise a child, it
takes the Village People."
Hey, guys?
I think I may have
gotten way too high.
Can somebody take me
to the hospital?
You're in a hospital.
Whoa.
How'd you do that?
I wonder why
we haven't heard anything.
They took Kathy to the delivery
room, like, an hour ago.
Sometimes the baby just
doesn't want to come out.
I mean, put yourself
in its position.
For nine months,
you've been floating
in the world's
nicest waterbed.
Then somebody opens a trap door,
all the water flows out,
a set of salad tongs grabs you
by the head and yanks you out,
and then some guy
you never seen before
starts slapping
you on the ass.
Reminds me of a trip
I took to Tijuana once.
Aw, look at how cute
that one is.
Yeah, she's got
a nice rack, too.
What are you looking at?
The hot nurse.
That baby.
Ugh! You guys are sick.
So have you guys decided
on a name for the baby yet?
Oh, no, not yet.
No.
It's such a big
responsibility.
I don't want
to give him a name
that other kids
can make fun of.
Well, bad news.
Every name can be made fun of.
That's not true.
Really?
How's your pond, Walden?
It's an intellectual insult,
but it still stings.
I was "Larry the fairy"
all through high school.
Oh, no way!
I was "Barry the fairy."
Somebody noticed
that you could rearrange
the letters of "Alan,"
and I became
"Little Anal Harper."
My name's "Herb."
Kids skipped the clever puns
and just shoved my head
down a toilet.
Well, I'm sure
there are plenty of names
that kids can't
make jokes about.
Mr. and Mr. Harper-Schmidt?
Yeah, nothing to
worry about there.
Just the hyphenated last name
of the two gay dads.
So how's Kathy?
She's doing fine.
So is your brand-new baby boy.
Oh, my God,
we got a boy!
I get a do-over for Jake!
I only have to worry
about one penis!
I like to wear
women's underwear!
What?
I thought we were
confessing things.
There he is.
Aw...
He's got your nose
and Alan's eyes.
Larry, I told you
before that...
Thank you, Larry.
Look at him.
He's so amazing.
I can't think of
anything more beautiful
than what I'm looking
at right now.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
It's true, that's the truth.
But how much more
beautiful would it be
if those two nurses just
started making out right now?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
How you doing?
I'm good.
Tired.
Sore.
Look at this little guy.
Can I hold him?
Uh, sure.
Oh, he is the cutest thing ever.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, hey... high-five.
You can owe me.
Welcome to the world,
little buddy.
We're gonna have
so much fun.
We're gonna go to
ball games together
and go swimming together
and pick up chick... ens
together.
Smile. Come on.
Okay, uh...
Oh, oh, oh.
Look at that picture.
The two most handsome
men in the world.
And they're both mine.
Oh, oh...
Oh, what's the matter?
Uh, maybe he wants his mommy.
Oh, all right,
come here, little buddy.
Uh, I think he might be hungry.
Oh, of course.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Okay, here.
There.
I miss him already.
Yeah, it's hard to let him go.
Actually, it's impossible.
Oh.
I am so sorry.
Wait. What, uh...
what just happened?
Did I... did I
miss something?
She's keeping the baby.
Uh...
But what-what
about law school?
The-the five-year plan?
After I saw this little guy...
the plan changed.
I mean, before, I couldn't
imagine my life with him.
Now I can't imagine it
without him.
But... but he's gonna
be a great dad.
Alan...
No, no. H-He loves him.
Alan, it's...
Okay, let's-let's just
approach this practically.
Um... how much for the kid?
Uh, I have, uh,
I have $32 on me.
I'm gonna need three dollars
for dinner at ampm,
but the rest is yours.
Believe me, I feel terrible.
You feel terrible?
We're-we're gonna be driving
home with an empty car seat.
And you know what's waiting
for us when we get there?
An empty nursery.
An empty crib.
An empty... uh, uh....
What's that Swedish thing
that, uh, that you
wear like a pouch,
to carry your baby
around like a kangaroo?
Bjorn.
An empty Bjorn!
An empty blue baby Bjorn!
Hard to say,
but even harder to face.
Alan, just... stop.
It's okay.
I wouldn't be able
to give him up either,
so I don't blame you.
Really?
I get it.
You're his mom.
I'm so sorry to put you
through all this.
Don't be sorry.
He's... lucky.
You're both...
very lucky.
This man is a saint.
A damn saint.
Let's go.
Say good-bye, Elliot.
More like "Smelliot."
Alan.
♪ Men. ♪
You doing okay?
Yeah.
Can you show me
the picture of him?
Oh, please, don't put yourself
through this.
Come on, just
one more time.
Okay.
Here.
Look at him.
He's perfect.
I'm sorry this didn't work out
as planned.
He still owes me a high-five.
Don't worry.
We'll find our kid.
I know.
In the meantime,
you're still married to me.
Yes, I am.
Why couldn't Kathy take you
and give me the baby?!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man